http://www.visitingangels.com/hillsborough/privacy-policy

Visiting Angels Hillsborough County, FL813-752-0008
Give Us a Review!
» READ ARTICLE
About Visiting Angels of Hillsborough County, FLAbout UsWhy Visiting AngelsVisiting Angels Reviews & TestimonialsHealth Care Reform InfoAlzheimer's AssociationCertified Senior AdvisorsYou’re in ControlWe’re ProactiveHome Health Care Referrals Senior Home Care ReferralsReferrals for In-Home Assisted Living CareEmpathetic Alzheimer’s Care ReferralsExpert Home Care ReferralsAt Home Care Experts
Senior Care in Sun City CenterCaregiver Sun City Center Our Referrals for Dementia Care Services in Brandon
How Home Care Works
Senior News
Fire Safety Tips for Seniors
» READ ARTICLE
How Home Care WorksWhat is Home CareHow Do I Get StartedLong Distance ServicesFAQsHow We AssistBrochure LibraryCostsOur CaregiversOur ExperienceOur CharacterHome Care Providers
Types of Care
Senior News
4 Tips to Help Seniors Transition Home After a Stroke
» READ ARTICLE
Types of CareHome Care ServicesElderly Companion Care ServicesPrivate Duty CareRespite CareLife Care NavigationLife Care Navigation OverviewCertified Palliative CareReady – Set – Go HomeSocial CareDementia CareAlzheimers Care ServicesEnd of Life CareFall Prevention
Resources
Senior News
Keeping Seniors Safe in Public During COVID-19
» READ ARTICLE
Senior ResourcesHints, Tips & AdviceArticles of InterestMedia Center
Caring Careers
Contact
Give Us a Review!
About
About UsWhy Visiting AngelsVisiting Angels Reviews & TestimonialsHealth Care Reform InfoAlzheimer's AssociationCertified Senior AdvisorsYou’re in ControlWe’re ProactiveHome Health Care Referrals Senior Home Care ReferralsReferrals for In-Home Assisted Living CareEmpathetic Alzheimer’s Care ReferralsExpert Home Care ReferralsAt Home Care Experts
Senior Care in Sun City CenterCaregiver Sun City Center Our Referrals for Dementia Care Services in Brandon
How Home Care Works
What is Home CareHow Do I Get StartedLong Distance ServicesFAQsHow We AssistBrochure LibraryCostsOur ExperienceOur CharacterHome Care Providers
Types of Care
Home Care ServicesElderly Companion Care ServicesPrivate Duty CareRespite CareLife Care Navigation OverviewCertified Palliative CareReady – Set – Go HomeSocial CareDementia CareAlzheimers Care ServicesEnd of Life CareFall Prevention
Caring Careers
Resources
Hints, Tips & AdviceArticles of InterestMedia Center
Our Story
About UsWhy Visiting AngelsOur Reviews
Contact
Contact UsClient FeedbackPrivacy PolicyHIPAA Privacy Practices
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to information collected online from users of this website (“Site”). In this policy, you can learn what kind of information we collect, when and how we might use that information, how we protect the information, and choices you have with respect to your personal information. By using or accessing the Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of use, including without limitation the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the collection, or use and disclosure of your information or personal information as set forth herein, you may not use this Site.
This Privacy Policy IS NOT the same as a Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices, which discusses how Visiting Angels uses and shares clients’ individually identifiable health information, among other things.  Your Visiting Angels’ Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices is available through another link called “HIPAA Privacy Practices,” which is located on the homepage of your Visiting Angels’ Site. You may also call your Visiting Angels’ offices at the phone number on the Site’s homepage and ask for a copy of the Notice of HIPAA Privacy Practices at any time.
1. General Tracking Information
We keep track of the pages visited by each user. Our web server automatically collects some information about you when you request pages from our server, including your IP address. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. We use this information to improve our Site by making it more responsive to the needs and preferences of our users. This information does not identify you personally.
2. Click Path Tracking
Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Visiting Angels and our affiliates, our marketing, testing and quality assurance partners, or our analytics, information technology and web monitoring service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. Mobile applications may also use cookies. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you and to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality. We use Local Storage also referred to as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use Local Storage to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LS’s.
We partner with third party ad networks to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner may use cookies, IP addresses, cookie identifiers, website activity, and/or Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.
3. Collection of Personal Information
If you choose to register on our Site, you will be asked to provide Personal Information which may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and phone number. We do not actively share Personal Information gathered from our Web servers. When you register, we will place your name in our mailing list and will send you an e-mail to the address you have provided to confirm your registration on our Site.
4. What we do with the Personal Information We Collect
We require Personal Information from you in order to learn more about how you use the Site; to measure areas of interest in our network and the services we provide; to understand the needs of our customers; to provide you with better service; and to help us with internal record keeping. If you register, your registration information may be used by Visiting Angels and our Franchisees and Master Franchisees for internal research purposes and may be compiled as part of our internal database system. In addition, we may send correspondence to the e-mail and / or street address you provide to us when registering on our Site. This correspondence may include newsletters, promotional offers, information on new features and services we provide, Site updates, responses to your e-mails, comments and opinions, and may also be used as a means of providing technical support. In certain instances, you will have an opportunity to limit these uses at the time your Personal Information is collected. You also may limit the correspondence by following the instructions in the "Opt-Out" Section below.
5. Sharing of Personal Information
We will share your Personal Information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties. We will not provide or sell any Personal Information to marketing research or bulk advertising sales companies. We will share your Personal Information with our Franchisees and Master Franchisees who are bound to protect such information from disclosure or misuse. We may share your Personal Information with third-party business partners who offer services in conjunction with those of Visiting Angels and who we believe may provide offers that may be of interest to you. As described above, you may limit this sharing by following the instructions in the "Opt-Out" Section below. We may also disclose Personal Information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Terms of Use, or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other website users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information to law-enforcement personnel and agencies when requested to do so or as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena or if Visiting Angels is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets. In any of these situations, registered users will be notified by e-mail of our intent to disclose information.
We may also provide your Personal Information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your Personal Information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
Links to Third Party Websites
Occasionally we may include on our Site a hyperlink (a "Link") or a banner advertisement ("Banner Ad") containing a Link which allows you to connect to the home page of third party website ("Third Party Site"), the website of a Franchisee ("Franchisee Site") or the website of a Master Franchisee ("Master Franchisee Site"). Visiting Angels provides these Links to you as a convenient method of accessing information that may be useful or of interest to you. This Privacy Policy and the practices that we follow under this Privacy Policy do not apply to Third Party Sites, Franchisee Sites or Master Franchisee Sites that are operated independently from Visiting Angels. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy, or opinions expressed on any Franchisee Site, Master Franchisee Site or Third Party Site or for the privacy practices of our Franchisees, Master Franchisees or any third party. We will not, and are under no obligation to, investigate, monitor or check the Franchisee Sites, Master Franchisee Sites or Third Party Sites for accuracy or completeness, or for any obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, indecent, profane, defamatory or unlawful content or materials. Inclusion of any Link or Banner Ad to a Third Party Site, or Franchisee Site or Master Franchisee Site that is placed on our Site does not imply approval or endorsement of the Third Party Site, Franchisee Site or Master Franchisee Site. You understand and agree that by clicking on a Link to a Third Party Site, Franchisee Site, or Master Franchisee Site you have left this Site, and the Visiting Angels Privacy Policy stated on this Site is no longer in effect.
Our Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your Personal Information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our hardware, software, and security infrastructure as well as our internal standards for this Site to meet current industry standards and technology. In addition, we will be using standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) certificates to secure all pages used for inputting user Personal Information. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between us will be free from unauthorized access by third parties.
Opt-Out
You may choose to have your name taken off of our registration list, cease receiving correspondence or newsletters from us or you can update or delete the Personal Information that you have provided to us, via one of the following methods:
Using the opt-out option in e-mails you receive from us;
Sending us an e-mail at: ecorbin@visitingangels.com
Writing to us at: Living Assistance Services, Inc., 937 Haverford Road, Suite 200, Bryn Mawr, PA 19010; or calling us toll free at: 1.800.365-4189
We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
What We Do with Your Browser’s Settings and Signals
As stated under “2. Click Path Tracking,” we use cookies to help gather information about visitors to our Site for demographics and to provide a better, more personalized experience for visitors and users of our Site. When you visit our Site, you may use browser settings that reject cookies or tracking, or alert you when a cookie is placed through your browser. However, if you use such browser settings, you may not be able to use or access all of the features and functionality of our Site. When you visit our Site, you may also use browser settings that block ads. However, if you use such browser settings, you may not be able to use or access all of the features and functionality of our Site. We reserve the right to change this policy and to further limit the features and functions of this Site, or to completely limit access to this Site, in response to such browser setting limitations in the future without prior notice. (See “Changes to this Privacy Policy,” below.)
Special Notice for Visitors Who Reside Outside the United States
We welcome users of this site from other countries outside of the United States. We may transfer your personal information to our service providers and others located in the U.S. or other countries for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Different countries have different privacy laws and requirements, and some, including the U.S., provide less legal protection for your personal information than others. Regardless of the country in which your personal information is collected, used, transferred or stored, information collected through this site will be protected by the terms of this Privacy Policy.
The California Consumer Privacy Act
The Cal. Civ. Code §1798.135: Do Not Sell My Info Act requires companies to include certain disclosures including "Do Not Sell My Info" links on their websites and mobile applications. Visiting Angels does not sell information that identifies who you are to anyone.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change or revise this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. The changes will be effective as of the revised date posted at the top of this policy. The changes we make will apply only to the personal information we collect after we have posted the revised version. Your use of this web site following any such change constitutes your consent to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. For this reason, it is important to review this Privacy Policy regularly.
Disclaimer
The data contained in our Site is for informational purposes only and is not represented to be error free. Visiting Angels attempts to ensure that the data provided or otherwise displayed on our Site is accurate. However, the Site and its contents are provided on an "as is, as available" basis. Use of the Site and its contents is at your sole risk. Visiting Angels does not warrant that any functions of the Site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that the Site will be free from viruses or other harmful components. Visiting Angels makes no warranties, either express or implied, concerning the content of the Site, including the accuracy, completeness, reliability or suitability of the Site.
Each Visiting Angels agency is a franchise that is independently owned and operated. The Franchisor, Living Assistance Services Inc., does not control or manage the day to day business operations of any Visiting Angels franchised agency.
Contact
Contact UsHIPAA Privacy PracticesClient FeedbackPrivacy Policy
Serving
Hillsborough County, FloridaVisiting Angels inSun City Center3830 Sun City Center Blvd#102Sun City Center, FL  33573Phone: 813-752-0008
You were such a comfort to me and my grandmother before her death. Your caregivers are a godsend!
About
About UsWhat is Home CareWhy Visiting AngelsOur ReviewsHealth Care Reform InfoAlzheimer's AssociationCertified Senior AdvisorsYou’re in ControlWe’re ProactiveHome Health Care Referrals Senior Home Care ReferralsReferrals for In-Home Assisted Living CareEmpathetic Alzheimer’s Care ReferralsExpert Home Care ReferralsAt Home Care Experts
Senior Care in Sun City CenterCaregiver Sun City Center Our Referrals for Dementia Care Services in Brandon
How Home Care Works
What is Home CareHow Do I Get StartedLong Distance ServicesFAQsHow We AssistBrochure LibraryCostsOur ExperienceOur CharacterHome Care Providers
Types of Care
Home Care ServicesElderly Companion Care ServicesPrivate Duty CareRespite CareCaring for Someone with Alzheimer'sLife Care Navigation OverviewCertified Palliative CareAlzheimer's FAQCaring For Someone with AlzheimersReady – Set – Go HomeSocial CareDementia CareAlzheimer's FAQAlzheimers Care ServicesEnd of Life CareFall Prevention
Resources
Hints, Tips & AdviceArticles of InterestMedia Center
Contact
Contact UsHIPAA Privacy PracticesClient FeedbackPrivacy Policy
Caring Careers
Each Visiting Angels agency is a franchise that is independently owned and operated. The Franchisor, Living Assistance Services Inc., does not control or manage the day to day business operations of any Visiting Angels franchised agency.
Living Assistance Services, Inc.
Copyright® 2020  |  Visiting Angels in Hillsborough County, FL  |  3830 Sun City Center Blvd #102  |  Sun City Center FL 33573  |  813-752-0008
Visiting Angels in Hillsborough County, FL3830 Sun City Center Blvd #102Sun City Center FL33573813-752-0008
